A Guide to the Frederic G. Melcher-Robert Frost Collection,
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Correspondence of Robert Frost, members of the Frost Family, and Frederic G. Melcher
  - Robert Frost to Frederic G. Melcher, [1935 Sep?], ALS, 3 pp. on 2 l. (Box-folder 1:67)
    Explains his "tangle" with Macmillan, over King Jasper, A Poem by Edwin Arlington Robinson, with an introduction by Robert Frost, "because it wasn't an appraisal, didn't mention King Jasper and didn't bring in enough Robinson," and their advertisement which says he will autograph their $7.50 edition for no additional payment. He also mentions that he is going to New York in October to make some records for Professor Hibbet at Columbia. Includes a carbon transcript of the letter.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, 1935 Sep 20, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 1:68)
    Advises Frost to not autograph the Macmillan books unless they pay him another two hundred dollars. Includes a carbon transcript of the letter.
  - Robert Frost, Amherst, Massachusetts, to Frederic G. Melcher, 1935 Nov 11, ALS, 1 p. (Box-folder 1:69)
    Plans to use his poem Departmental, which will appear in The Yale Review, for a Christmas greeting. Includes a carbon transcript of the letter.
  - Lesley Frost, Rockford College, Rockford, Illinois, to Frederic G. Melcher, 1936 Mar 13, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l. (Box-folder 1:70)
    Asks for the article and pictures back, hopes to see him in April when she is going to Cambridge for her spring vacation with her mother and father.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1936 Mar 18, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 1:71)
    Hopes he is comfortable in his new surroundings, finds it exciting that over 50,000 copies of Frost's new volume are going out for sale all at once, tells of hearing from Lesley, and mentions a visit with Carl Sandburg last week.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Lesley Frost, Rockford, Illinois, 1936 Mar 19, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 1:72)
    Apologizes for keeping her photographs so long and asks if he can have one made of her father and mother for his personal collection. Also mentions that the Book-of-the-Month Club has taken Far Range for distribution which should certainly help the sales of Collected Poems.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1936 Mar 25, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 1:73)
    Wishes Frost a happy 61st birthday, congratulates him on being the guest of honor on the 300th anniversary of Harvard University, discusses the new edition of Untermeyer, which contains over 30 of Frost's poems, and [Charles R.] Green's bibliography.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Amherst, Massachusetts, 1937 Apr 15, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 1:74)
    Refers to Frost's time in Texas, and the pleasure of his friend, Rosengren, of San Antonio, at the pleasure of meeting Frost, and his plans on having David Randall of Scribner's to review Green's bibliography.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Amherst, Massachusetts, 1937 May 4, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 1:75)
    Congratulates Frost on winning the Pulitzer Prize for Poetry for A Further Range.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, South Shaftsbury, Vermont, 1937 Sep 27, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 1:76)
    Expresses his pleasure that Thornton is using his Colophon article in the volume they are publishing, mentions an Horatio Alger title that his book scout has found, "Out for Business, or Robert Frost's Strange Career." Also mentions a new article by [Robert S.] Newdick and an early Frost family photograph.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Amherst, Massachusetts, 1937 Nov 5, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 1:77)
    Notices from the Book Fair program that Frost will be in town soon and hope he will have time to visit Melcher at this home.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Gainesville, Florida, 1938 Jan 6, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:1)
    Hopes that the Frosts are basking in the sunlight and that Elinor is better, mentions seeing Frost's photograph and an article by Bernard De Voto used in the current Holt advertisement, and briefly discusses a book about Edward Thomas by R.P. Eckert.
  - Robert Frost, Gainesville, Florida, to Frederic G. Melcher, 1938 Apr 14, ANS, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:2)
    "I shall be along by next Tuesday. I shall want to thank you a lot when I see you," with a printed card announcing funeral services for Elinor Frost to be held at Johnson Chapel, Amherst College, at 3 o'clock on Friday, April 22, 1938. Includes a carbon transcript of the letter.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Lesley Frost, Gainesville, Florida, 1938 Apr 28, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:3)
    Offers suggestions about future employment, specifically with the Providence Booke Shop belonging to Mrs. Benjamin C. Clough, and the Kirkus Review service owned by Virginia Kirkus.
  - Lesley Frost, Gainesville, Florida, to Frederic G. Melcher, 1938 Apr 28, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l. (Box-folder 2:4)
    Thanks him for his prompt reply and his suggestions about future employment. She also shares some of her interests, especially about the Providence Booke Shop.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Lesley Frost, Gainesville, Florida, 1938 May 3, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:5)
    Informs her that he has asked Virginia Kirkus to write with more details about her service.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Lesley Frost, Gainesville, Florida, 1938 May 26, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:6)
    Asks is she is interested in selling the Pittsfield business.
  - Lesley Frost, Gainesville, Florida, to Frederic G. Melcher, 1938 Jun 2, ALS, 2 pp. on 2 l. (Box-folder 2:7)
    Plans on arriving in New York next week and wants to meet with John Joseph Hagedorn and his wife over selling her business and also with Mrs. Kirkus.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, South Shaftsbury, Vermont, 1938 Jul 5, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:8)
    Mails a Pickering volume, thanks Frost for a poem and offers his home as a sort of between stop if he needs one.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, South Shaftsbury, Vermont, 1938 Aug 9, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:9)
    Refers to a full month vacation at Cape Cod and a visit from Lesley, who has decided to take a position in Washington, D.C., another offer of his home as a place of refuge to write, and asks if he would consider giving a talk for the Unity Institute Course in Montclair.
  - Robert Frost, South Shaftsbury, Vermont, to Frederic G. Melcher, 1938 Aug 12, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l. (Box-folder 2:10)
    Frost finds Melcher's offer of a place to work at his home attractive but feels his restless mood would prevent him from accepting, wants to do the talk for Melcher in Montclair if they can find a good time, and gives his current engagements. Includes a carbon transcript of the letter.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Concord Corners, Vermont, 1938 Aug 22, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:11)
    Suggests March 31st as a good date for his visit to Montclair to speak and mentions obtaining a colored photograph of Frost by Blackstone. Includes a carbon transcript of the letter.
  - Robert Frost, St. Botolph Club, Boston, Massachusetts, to Frederic G. Melcher, [1938 Oct?], ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l. (Box-folder 2:12)
    Agrees to speak on March 24th, mentions his desperate restlessness, and addresses at which he may be reached, "But Amherst no more!" Includes a carbon transcript of the letter.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Boston, Massachusetts, 1938 Oct 14, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:13)
    Melcher is pleased he will see Frost at the Columbia Library School and is glad Frost is living on Mt. Vernon Street, familiar to him from his days at Lauriat's. Includes a carbon transcript of the letter.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Boston, Massachusetts, 1938 Dec 22, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:14)
    Reports about William Sloane, formerly of Farrar and Rinehart, and his plans for Holt & Company and the advertising for Frost's books.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Boston, Massachusetts, 1939 Mar 2, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:15)
    Writes that he is very excited about Frost's introduction to the Holt Collected Poems, but was bothered that Holt used a different font of type to set the new section "using Linotype because it is less expensive than Monotype."
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Boston, Massachusetts, 1939 Apr 11, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:16)
    Discusses an interview that Frost gave at the Maplewood school and a poem that a student, Barbara Norton, had written.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Boston, Massachusetts, 1939 May 12, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:17)
    Refers to the Ralph Waldo Emerson Fellow in Poetry awarded to Frost by Harvard University.
  - Robert Frost, Boston, Massachusetts, to Frederic G. Melcher, [1939 Nov 27], ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l., with envelope (Box-folder 2:18)
    Expresses his shock and dismay that Melcher has been seriously ill, mentions writing a poem for a Christmas card for Joe Blumenthal, but adds, "Don't let this encourage you to think I am writing any more. I haven't got over hating paper pen and ink yet." Includes a carbon transcript of the letter.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Boston, Massachusetts, 1940 Mar 15, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:19)
    Refers to his visit with Frost and his concern that he take regular meals.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Boston, Massachusetts, 1940 Apr 2, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:20)
    Enjoys Louis Untermeyer's book and the Scholastic Magazine Poetry Corner featuring Frost, with its good photograph of Frost.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1941 Nov 14, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:21)
    Sends Frost a copy of Emerson's Poems, London, 1847, for his enjoyment.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Dartmouth College, Hanover, New Hampshire, 1944 Mar 7, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:22)
    Checks on several questions about autographed poems in Frost editions sold by questionable booksellers, especially two dedicated to E. Ording and H. Conti. Includes a carbon transcript of the letter.
  - Robert Frost, Cambridge Massachusetts, to Frederic G. Melcher, 1944 Mar 22, TLS, 2 pp. on 2 l. (Box-folder 2:23)
    Replies that he has done things for E. Ording on request and wonders if H. Conti is not H. Knauti, who had aroused their suspicion. Shares his plans to lecture at Chicago University on the subject "Where is the Place of Ideals and Who is Their Keeper?" and mentions several other speaking engagements. Includes a carbon transcript of the letter.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1944 Mar 23, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:24)
    Thanks him for his comments about E. Ording and H. Knauti, which he will pass on to his friend Captain [Louis Henry] Cohn, who specializes in Frost material.
  - Robert Frost, Key West, Florida, to Frederic G. Melcher, 1945 [Feb 22?], ALS, 3 pp. on 3 l., with envelope (Box-folder 2:25)
    Agrees to a birthday party at the P.E.N. club if he only has to read a poems or two to pay his way, and if Melcher can work it out with Henry Holt and Company. Frost tells about the other commitments he has in New York at the same time period. Talks about being with Prescott and Lillian on a small five acre farm in Florida where Prescott is attending the University of Miami.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1945 Jul 13, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:26)
    Discusses his speaking tour of England which was arranged by The National Book League. He also tells of his presentation of their joint Christmas card of "Two Tramps" to John Masefield and his suggestion that the National Book League should elect Robert Frost as the first honorary life member, which they did on the spot. Also mentions the new edition of Come In which he gave as gifts while on his trip.
  - Robert Frost, Ripton, Vermont, to Frederic G. Melcher, 1945 Jul 20, TLS, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:27)
    Discusses Melcher's report of his trip to England and his pleasure at John Masefield's interest in his poetry. Includes a carbon transcript of the letter.
  - Robert Frost, Hanover, New Hampshire, to Frederic G. Melcher, 1945 Nov 23, ALS, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:28)
    Tells Melcher not to worry about his idea about staying at his house for awhile since he is not sure he could be lured so close to New York and says he is glad that Melcher likes the new president. Also present is an empty envelope addressed to Melcher in Frost's hand, postmarked November 20, 1945.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1946 Oct 21, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:29)
    Thinks Frost must be pleased with the Pocket Book of Poems, which uses the Untermeyer selection and introduction and the Cosgrave pictures. He also enjoyed the article by Frost about writing poetry in the October Atlantic.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Ripton, Vermont, 1947 Jun 2, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:30)
    Identifies H. Kauti as Van Nosdall, a famous faker in the book business.
  - Robert Frost Note to Frederic G. Melcher, 1949 Nov 16 (Box-folder 2:31)
    Written on Melcher's Place Card at a dinner given to Frost by Henry Holt & Company at the University Club
  - Robert Frost Telegram, Cambridge, Massachusetts, to Frederic Melcher, 1951 Mar 16, Asks to be excused from the Book Sellers Convention. (Box-folder 2:32)
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1951 Mar 19, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:33)
    Understands why Frost cannot make it to the Book Sellers Convention in May.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Ripton, Vermont, 1952 Sep 26, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:34)
    Provides the results of his investigation of Mr. Kerti, who requested a signed portrait.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1953 Mar 3, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:35)
    Mentions seeing Frost in the Times that morning and that P.E.N. wants to honor Frost at their cocktail party.
  - Frederic G. Melcher to Robert Frost, Ripton, Vermont, 1956 Jun 27, TL, carbon, 1 p. (Box-folder 2:36)
    Thanks Frost for his contribution to the auction held by the American Library Association to raise money for a children's librarian scholarship in Melcher's name.
  - Lesley Frost to Marguerite Melcher, 1963 Christmas, ANS (Box-folder 2:37)
    On a black and white postcard of Robert Frost's cabin in Ripton, Vermont, "All best wishes to you and yours, Marguerite. We both know what it means to lose great men."
  - Robert Frost to Frederic G. Melcher, n.d., ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l. (Box-folder 2:38)
    Reports that he has received a "flood of Americana" from Goodspeeds, a good book from Dal Hitchcock, and the Pueblo Potter from Melcher. Includes a carbon transcript of the letter.
  - Elinor Frost, New Haven, Connecticut, to Frederic G. Melcher, n.y. Apr 4, ALS, 2 pp. on 1 l. (Box-folder 2:39)
    Writes that they did not leave Key West as soon as expected, she is visiting Irma while Robert is staying around Washington, D.C., and she is still very weak.
  - Elinor Frost, Ann Arbor, Michigan, to Marguerite Melcher, n.y. Jun 4, ALS, 8 pp. on 2 l. (Box-folder 2:40)
    Updates her about Marjorie's bouts of ill health, thanks her for writing to Marjorie, and tells her that they have decided to give up the fellowship at Michigan and move closer to the children, especially Carol. Robert has to lecture at Amherst for six or eight weeks next year, as well as other New England colleges.
  - Elinor Frost, Ann Arbor, Michigan, to Frederic G. Melcher, n.y. Oct 26, ALS, 3 pp. on 1 l. (Box-folder 2:41)
    They will leave for Amherst after an absence of four months, and will remain there until April 1st. They had a very good visit with Lillian during their summer in California. Includes a carbon transcript of the letter.
  - Frost Family Christmas Card to the Melchers, Christmas, in a postcard format (Box-folder 2:42)
- Series III: Miscellaneous Papers concerning Robert Frost
  - Advertisement and Order Form Postcard- A Witness Tree New Poems by Robert Frost, [1942], printed (Box-folder 2:43)
  - Advertisement for Phonograph Recordings of Robert Frost reading twelve of his favorite poems and other recordings, 1935, n.d., printed and typescript (Box-folder 2:44)
    Available from Erpi Picture Consultants, Inc.
  - Advertisement for A Way Out A One Act Play by Robert Frost 1929, printed (Box-folder 2:45)
    Published by The Harbor Press.
  - Advertising Booklet- "Robert Frost The Man and His Work" from Henry Holt & Company, [1923], printed (Box-folder 2:46)
  - Article - "Robert Frost and His Books" by Frederic G. Melcher, 1930 May, Galley proof, 8 sheets, formerly laid in Part 2 of The Colophon in which it was published (oversize)
  - Article- "Robert Frost for Collectors" by Frederic G. Melcher, [ca. 1930], TMsS, 12 pp. (Box-folder 2:47)
    Annotated by the author, later printed in Colophon, May 1930
  - Article- "Robert Frost and His Printers" by Ray Nash, 1946 Jan, printed (Box-folder 2:48)
    In The Book Collector's Packet, Volume 4 Number 5, pages 10-12, signed by Robert Frost and inscribed to Fred Melcher,
  - Article-"Robert Frost's Hilltop" by Dorothy Canfield Fisher with Woodcuts by J.J. Lankes, n.d., printed (Box-folder 2:49)
  - Articles of Tribute to Robert Frost in Saturday Review1963 Feb 23 (Box-folder 2:50)
  - Articles concerning Robert Frost, printed and electrostatic copies 1923-1950 (Box-folder 2:51)
  - Articles concerning Robert Frost, printed and electrostatic copies 1951-1962, n.d. (Box-folder 2:52)
  - Articles concerning Robert Frost by Robert S. Newdick, 1935-1937, printed (Box-folder 2:53)
  - Bibliographical Information concerning Robert Frost, A Boy's Will and North of Boston, 1930, typescript (Box-folder 2:54)
    Collected by J. Brussels in London and given to Frederic Melcher for use in the Amherst Library bibliography.
  - Booklet of Robert Frost Poems printed for a dinner held in New York in honor of his 85th Birthday, 1959 Mar 26, TLS, printed. (Box-folder 2:55)
    With a letter from Edgar T. Rigg, President, Henry Holt and Company, Inc., to Frederic Melcher, March 6, 1959, about the celebration, and a copy of the menu.
  - Bookplate belonging to Robert Frost, n.d. (Box-folder 2:56)
    Inscribed "Robert Frost to Fred Melcher".
  - Bookplate designed by J.J. Lankes for Robert Frost n.d. (Box-folder 2:57)
    Showing the first house belonging to Frost in South Shaftsbury, Vermont.
  - Chronology for Robert Frost 1935, 1945 (Box-folder 2:58)
  - Compositions concerning Robert Frost 1913-1961, n.d. (Box-folder 2:59)
  - Description of poet Thomas Ferril by Robert Frost 1934 Oct 13 (Box-folder 2:60)
    Quoted in Literary Notes Yale University Press.
  - Drawing of Robert Frost by Helen Wilson 1928 (Box-folder 2:61)
    Published as a supplement to The Bookman.
  - Ephemera concerning The Jones Library, Amherst, Massachusetts, the Robert Frost Collection and the Committee for the Robert Frost Fund ca. 1935-1959, n.d. (Box-folder 2:62)
  - Exhibition Announcements from the Grolier Club and Duke University Library 1939, 1950 (Box-folder 2:63)
  - Exhibition Catalogs concerning Robert Frost at Baker Library, Dartmouth College, Hanover, New Hampshire and Reis Library, Alleghany College, Meadville, Pennsylvania 1938, 1944 (Box-folder 2:64)
  - Guest List and Seating Arrangements for Robert Frost's 70th Birthday at the P.E.N. Club Dinner 1945 Mar 26 (Box-folder 2:65)
  - Guest List and Seating Arrangements for Robert Frost's 80th Birthday Banquet 195[4?] Mar 26 (Box-folder 2:66)
  - Honorary Degrees of Robert Frost Listed 1947-1961 (Box-folder 2:67)
  - Inscription by Robert Frost in the unique copy of his first book, Twilight, printed in Antiquarian Bookman1952 Jan (Box-folder 2:68)
  - Invitations and Programs for Robert Frost's 50th Birthday Dinner, one signed by Willa Cather 1925 Mar 26 (Box-folder 2:69)
  - Invitation, Seating Arrangement and Guest List for a Dinner for Robert Frost at The New School For Social Research 1937 Nov 30 (Box-folder 2:70)
  - Invitation to the Wedding of Phyllis Marie Gordon and William Prescott Frost 1947 Jun 12 (Box-folder 2:71)
  - Invitation, Program and Speeches for the Dedication of the Robert Frost Room in the Jones Library, Amherst, Massachusetts 1958, 1959 Oct 21 (Box-folder 3:1)
  - Invitation to the Memorial Service for Robert Frost at Johnson Chapel, Amherst College 1963 Feb 17 (Box-folder 3:2)
  - Invitations and Tickets to Lectures and Other Events featuring Robert Frost 1939-1958 (Box-folder 3:3)
  - News clippings concerning Robert Frost 1916-1963, n.d. (Box-folder 3:4)
  - Note by Helen Melvin Moody concerning Robert Frost and his poem The Later Minstrel and its use at chapel at the Pinkerton Academy, [post 1907], photostatic copy (Box-folder 3:5)
  - Notice of "Robert Frost in A Tribute to Tagore" in celebration of the 100th Anniversary of the birth of Rabindranath Tagore 1961 April 19 (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Photograph of Robert Frost 1916 (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Photograph of an Oil Portrait of Robert Frost by James Chapin (1887-1975) 1930 (Box-folder 3:8)
    With an exhibition card listing the painting, January 20, 1930- February 8, 1930.
  - Photograph of Mr. and Mrs. Robert Frost in the Old Book Room, Maddox House, Rockford, Illinois 1935 Dec 7 (Box-folder 3:9)
  - Photograph of Robert Frost, Harvey Allen and Du Bose Heywood 1936 Jan, "Three Literary Lights" meet in Miami, Florida, at the International Airport. (Box-folder 3:10)
  - Photograph of the Amherst Home of Robert Frost and a group shot of Robert Frost with Joseph Auslander, Audrey Wardemann, David Morton, and Robert Francis by Lincoln W. Barnes 1936 (Box-folder 3:11)
  - Photographs of Robert Frost supplied by Henry Holt and Company, New York 1937 Mar (Box-folder 3:12)
  - Photograph of a Portrait of Robert Frost by Ercole Cartotto (1889-1946), an Italian artist who lives in Darien, Connecticut with an office in New York City 1938 (Box-folder 3:13)
  - Photograph of an Oil Painting of Robert Frost by A. Allyn Bishop purchased by the Jones Library of Amherst in 1942 [1942] (Box-folder 3:14)
  - Photograph of Robert Frost in his study in the Baker Library, Dartmouth College with his students 1943 Oct 2 (Box-folder 3:15)
  - Photograph of Robert Frost at the Agnes Scott College Library 1945 Jan 26 (Box-folder 3:16)
  - Photograph of Robert Frost receiving the "Author Meets the Critics" Literary Award, by Bertis Greene 1949 (Box-folder 3:17)
  - Photograph of Robert Frost with Raymond Holden, Newport, New Hampshire, First Annual Literary Festival Used Book Sale 1956 Oct 11 (Box-folder 3:18)
  - Photograph of Robert Frost used on the book jacket of You Come Too[1959] (Box-folder 3:19)
  - Photographs of Robert Frost and Frederic G. Melcher at Syracuse University receiving their Honorary Degrees from Chancellor William P. Tolley, 1959 (Box-folder 3:20)
    With two copies of the program.
  - Photograph of Robert Frost, seated with hands clasped n.d. (Box-folder 3:21)
  - Photograph of a Portrait of Robert Frost painted by Allen F. Rader for Howard G. Schmitt n.d. (Box-folder 3:22)
  - Pictures of Robert Frost from published print sources 1946-1962, n.d. (Box-folder 3:23)
  - Press Releases and Book Notes from Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc. and Henry Holt and Company concerning Robert Frost 1936, 1962 (Box-folder 3:24)
  - Press Releases from the Library of Congress concerning Robert Frost 1955-1962 (Box-folder 3:25)
  - Press Release from the Poetry Society of America concerning the $1000 Robert Frost Annual Poetry Award 1961 May 15 (Box-folder 3:26)
  - Press Release Typescripts concerning Robert Frost 1938, 1953 (Box-folder 3:27)